[Music]
ICC
Lombard
launches 14 new products in the healthcare and corporate sectors. The company
's technologically enabled and innovative
insurance offerings will
revolutionize the customer experience.
Abhishek, Vice President of the company,
said that the current era of the insurance industry is a great time to reimagine new positions
and possibilities. We have
appointed a nodal officer for Bihar. We have been given the responsibility to conduct awareness
programs on how we can promote insurance in Bihar and
how far we
can take it to the villages.
Our team is working diligently on this.
As you know,
Bihar is a very large state in
terms of population. But if you look at the current situation,
we are not in a very good position in the insurance sector. So right now,
we are all working
together and on top of this, we are doing all these
activities through awareness programs in Bihar. We are getting
road construction done, distributing helmets,
going to schools in villages and installing purifiers.
We have started many activities
and all the companies are working on this. All the
general insurance companies in Bihar have done so that  By getting
organized, we
could take insurance forward in Bihar. What
we have now is
unlimited,
but through bandages, when we were
moving ahead, one thing that the pendant has
taught Shikha Diya is that we have understood that
today,
without technology, we cannot do anything,
we cannot do anything, and this is only
insurance. If you go to any video, you will
see everything - auto, aviation, FMCG, very much, everything is
connected through technology. So, we are also in this direction
that let's go, we have already invested a lot in ICC numbering
technology
and we
want to trade everything through technology. We
also want to
become a payment company, completely everything from claim
settlement to technology, we have
invested in this technology and we will
take this thing to another level.
We think that it is not just our banking
facilities and insurance,
through technology you will see all the modern companies like Amazon
etc.
[Praise]
We  It should be given to the people so that in today's time, if
you need to
go to the customer and tell him that
whatever service I need, I am getting it within two or three minutes.
So, that is the reason for
your investment. That is the reason for your
not pushing. If you want to come in and contact me, I will definitely come back to the
contact of this program. This program is
a project of IIT, where this
number
project will be done in Bihar and trips will do
everything. But there are many programs ahead,
many activities are being done. There is a
daughter of cricket on 18th, in whose big one
I will tell you some setting. And there are
many activities ahead too. We will benefit in Bihar
only in Patna. Across
Bihar, across the
villages and townships, you will see
that the awareness of insurance is in
every village, every place,
every house, saving water,
not Panihari but Tripura also. If I
talk only about individual health insurance, then
our penetration in health insurance is less than 1%. Keep in
mind,
our penetration in India is
approximately 25%
in Bihar.  I am
telling you this by adding all the companies after excluding 1%
[Music]
and
for further expansion
[Music] there
are many different plans so if you see if
someone between 18 to 25 years of age has given Rs. 3 lakhs
[Music]
your premium will be around Rs. 10, there is
no delay in 18 years, right sir, in 35
years
[Music]
what am I telling you, now when she becomes an adult, it will be included in that,
sir, no
one will say how much or what will be the
premium in this, it
is fine
[Music]